- [Announcer]Introducing the new
BrainOp chiputilizing Lumerex's
patented AI
combined with cutting
edge microchip technology.
Simplifying the lives of
users around the globe
with an advanced and
intuitive interface
that covers everything
from fitness biometrics
to web browsing, to
everyday purchases.
With automatic scanning
technology that allows you
to seamlessly interact
with your world.
It's now available
in most countries.
Use it across the globe or
anywhere life takes you.
From the company
that brought you
the revolutionary NexusTrack
that reinvented
the travel industry
with high speed
capsule transports.
Now introducing
the BrainOp chip.
Unlock your mind.
Simplify your life.
Achieve excellence.
Contact Lumerex today to
schedule your appointment
and join the future.
BrainOp designed and
manufactured by Lumerex.
(dramatic music)
(static buzzing)
(suspenseful music)
(ominous music)
[Guard] - Stop.
(intense music)
Well, sit down then.
Put your fucking hands
in the fucking cuffs
and your feet.
Oh, that's a good boy.
Hey?
- Alright, convicts.
Welcome on board the NexusTrack.
Alright, sit tight ladies.
We'll be out of your hair soon
and you animals can enjoy
your final moments together
before you spend the
rest of eternity in hell.
I don't give a flying
fucking to a rolling donut
about any of you,
so you do not want
to test me.
- Oh, no, no, no.
You are gonna be on your
best fucking behavior.
Ain't you, convicts?
- Flynn, it's my first
time on the NexusTrack.
- Well,
congratu-fucking-lations, Rook.
Better than the shit stain
buses we used to ride.
- And they got passengers
mixed up with prisoners
mixed up with cargo in one tube.
What do you think is
gonna go wrong, man?
- Same tube,
separate components.
They'll link up
to the DC capsule,
then offload at the gas
chamber, quick and easy.
Settle your stomach, fairy boy.
(prisoner laughs)
- [Boss] Bring in the
last two and lock 'em up.
(suspenseful music)
- Woo!
Yeah! (laughs)
- Let's go!
- Woo!
(electricity zapping)
- Yeah man! Serve it up.
- Jesus Christ!
- Fuck those pigs up!
(intense music)
(electricity zapping)
(dramatic music)
(ominous music)
- Now that you're done
having your little outburst,
I'm gonna have to
leave you ladies.
Enjoy the ride.
Get the body and let's go.
Seal the door tight behind you.
(suspenseful music)
(intense synth music)
(NexusTrack roaring)
(prisoner laughing)
(intense synth music)
(intense synth music continues)
(dramatic music)
(light music)
(display beeping)
- Well, it can't be that bad.
- It's like herding cats.
And now these two show up
late, they're captains.
- We weren't really
that different.
I mean, you certainly
weren't an angel.
Do you remember what
you did to Mrs. Leary?
You were a fucking monster.
- (laughs) Okay, yeah.
We stirred shit up,
but we would never be late for
the train to the nationals.
- Mm.
- I dunno,
something's not right.
- Yeah.
Well, I still think we
should've had them travel
with the assistant coaches.
- No, I made them captains.
It's my responsibility.
I need to make sure
that they get there.
This whole routine falls
apart without them.
- You're very hard on yourself.
- You know, if it's one
thing the military taught me,
is personal responsibility.
It's my fault.
Or maybe they need someone else.
Maybe they don't
respect me enough.
What?
- Tessa, you're a great coach.
The girls love you.
- Yeah, just not
enough to show up
for the most important
day of the year.
- Cut 'em some slack.
It's their first offense.
Got a whole trip to DC to find
out what's going on, okay?
Forget about it. Drop it, yeah?
- Yeah.
- That's why we're here.
- Oh yeah?
Then we're totally screwed.
- [Heather] If we miss this
train, we are totally screwed.
The coaches will
actually kill us.
- [Mary] They can't kill
us, we're the captains.
- We should have
been with the team.
You know, they stayed to
escort us like little kids.
That is so embarrassing.
- Speaking of embarrassing,
about what I said
earlier, I, I just-
- I don't really
wanna talk about it.
- Yeah, well that's the problem.
- Hey, this is us.
- Whoa.
They're doing that chip
check-in thing already?
- Yep.
And force feeding us propaganda.
- [Announcer]To everyday
purchases with automatic-
- What a crock.
- Technology that allows you
to seamlessly interact
with your world.
It's now available
in most countries.
Use it across the globe or
anywhere life takes you.
From the company
that brought you
the revolutionary NexusTrack
that reinvented
the travel industry
with high speed
capsule transports.
Now introducing
the BrainOp chip.
Unlock your mind.
Simplify your life.
Achieve excellence.
Contact Lumerex today to
schedule your appointment
and join the future.
BrainOp designed and
manufactured by Lumerex.
- Mandatory in
five years, watch.
- I am never getting a chip.
- [Announcer]Last
call for passengers
on the 6:15 PM NexusTrack
to Washington DC.
Please report to platform
three immediately.
- Oh shit, we gotta go.
- Come on.
[Security]- Chip detected.
[Annoucer] - Last call for
passegers on the 6:15 PM
NexusTrack to Washington DC.
Please report to platform
three immediately.
This is the final
NexusTrack of the day.
(both laughing)
- Hi.
Stop.
- How old is he?
- Equipped for the modern age
with cutting edge technology
that syncs with your biochem.
It's the safest way to travel.
- Oh, come on. Really?
- No, I watched the
news last night.
What's his name? Senator Hillin.
He said that biotech
is the new future.
- Oh, so the news and
the politicians said it,
it must be true.
- It's creepy.
- God, where are these girls?
- Where are the coaches?
- They said platform
three at 6:00 PM.
- If we had the chip,
we would've never
have missed the train.
- Yeah, maybe.
But at least we're
still 100% human.
- (laughs) With
your love for tech,
I'm surprised you weren't
first in line to get one.
- Yeah, no, thank you.
That is a hard pass.
- Yeah, I'll go down fighting
before anyone chips me.
- Okay, Miss Badass.
I take it the self-defense
courses are working?
- Yeah, they're working.
- Okay.
Okay, I wanna show
you something.
- Excuse you.
- Hello, Susanna.
What would you like?
- Diet soda and Nutri-Bar.
- Thank you Susanna.
(vending machine whirs)
Have a nice day.
- No wait, no.
My Nutri-Bar is stuck.
(alarm blaring)
- [Michele AI]Please
do not shake the machine
or I will have to
notify security.
- Instant karma. (laughs)
- Watch this.
It's my new Data Dagger.
This is the closest
thing to a chip
as I'm ever gonna need to get.
(device beeping)
(vending machine whirs)
- Look at you, Miss Hacker.
You know this is illegal, right?
- No, it's not.
That bitch paid for it.
(Mary laughs)
(cellphone ringing)
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Hey.
- [Donna] Let me guess you're
not coming. - Yeah, no, of
course I'm coming.
- [Donna] We've
heard that before.
Then I get a last minute
call just like this.
- I'm an Interpol agent, Donna.
What do you expect me to do
when a hostage is taken at a
gas station I happen to be at?
I mean, should I just walk away?
- [Donna] Then there's the time
you got involved in
a road rage incident.
- Oh no. Come on,
that's not fair.
That wasn't, no, it
wasn't a road rage.
I was involved in
a terror attack.
- I can't do this anymore.
- Donna.
- [Donna] We can't do
this anymore to her, Gray.
- Hey, I don't
wanna fight. Okay?
- [Donna]No more
excuses, no more heroics.
- Yeah, I'm, I'm right
here at the train
and I'm boarding
the next capsule.
- [Donna] Just get here
and see your daughter.
- Okay.
I'll see you at the DC station.
- [Donna] You can
take a ride share.
(cellphone beeps)
- How nice.
- [Michele AI] Chip detected.
(device beeps)
(device blares)
- Oh, what the fuck?
- No BrainOp chip detected.
Kindly join the back of
the non-chipped line.
- You son of a bitch.
I'm not going to the back
of that fucking line.
- Please refrain from profanity.
- Sir, sir, you
need to calm down.
(dramatic music)
Stop that punk!
- Whoa! Whoa!
(NexusTrack officer shouting)
(kick thuds)
- [Rod] Bitch.
- There you ladies are.
- Did you see that?
- Coach is such a badass.
- Thank you, ma'am,
but I have this handled.
- You didn't do shit 'til Coach
kicked that guy's face in.
- Nice moves.
I didn't know they taught
that in cheer camp.
- They don't.
That was from two tours
in the Middle East.
- Thanks for your service.
I take it you're retired now?
- Yeah, I've got
other missions now.
Trying to get my girls
to DC for nationals.
- Alright, they're
in good hands.
Ladies.
- So, what's the excuse now?
(NexusTrack whirring)
(suspenseful music)
(keypad beeping)
(door clicks)
(keypad beeps)
(door whirs)
- About bloody time.
The passengers will be
boarding in 10 minutes.
Where's Daryl?
- I'm sorry.
- Huh?
(punch thuds)
(kick thuds)
(suspenseful music)
(computer beeps)
- I'm in.
- [Lachlan]Very good.
It's about time.
- Why can't you
just use your AI?
- AI cannot hack AI.
You of all people
should know that.
It takes an erratic human brain
to circumvent the position
of the computer, Mik.
- I don't want to
do this, Lachlan.
- [Lachlan] I understand
you don't want to do it,
and believe me I do,
but you'll do it for your
daughter's sake, will you not?
And if you do what I ask,
she'll be taken care of.
- After I do this, we are done?
- You hack the mainframe
and get me the access
that I need and,
yeah, we're done, Mik.
- You will get it soon.
(suspenseful music)
(upbeat music)
- Hey.
You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
No, I'm good.
- Okay.
- Well,
Coach, can we just,
can we talk about
something really quick?
- Of course.
- Um, things at home
have been kind of tough.
My parents have
been arguing a lot.
- You can tell me anything.
- It's just money problems
and I feel like I'm
caught in the middle of it
and now it's affecting
my friendships
and honestly, it's just
affecting everything.
- Is that why you
two missed the train?
- Yeah, kind of.
Oh God, it was so embarrassing.
We got in this huge fight
and then the taxi left.
- Okay, well next time
can you call us please?
- Yes.
- We were worried about you.
- I know, it's just, it's
hard to be the cheer captain
that everybody expects me to be
when I am literally falling
apart on the inside.
- Well, the good thing
about being a cheer captain
means that you don't
have to be perfect.
Okay?
Your team respects
and admires you,
not because of
your cheer skills,
but because of the
person that you are.
Remember that.
- Okay. Thank you.
I, that really means a lot.
- Nationals may
be a competition,
but you know, it's also a
chance for us to get together,
and make unforgettable memories.
So focus on that. Okay?
- Okay, okay.
I'll give it my all.
And I'm really, really grateful
to have you as my
coach and my friend.
And I promise you, we will
not let you down again at all.
- You're good.
- Okay. You sure?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(keyboard clacking)
(display beeping)
- Hacking civilian
chips might take awhile.
I've started the
public profile hack
so you could gain
access within the hour.
- Do you feel like telling
me what happened today?
- We got into it again.
- What about?
You guys are supposed
to be best friends.
- Just feels like
we're growing apart.
- In what way?
- She's just so into tech.
I could try to keep
up, but I can't.
It's just never enough.
Like I even went and tried
and it's just, I don't know.
It's stupid. Nevermind.
- You know, best
friends aren't always
supposed to have
everything in common.
How do you think I
felt when Tessa told me
she was joining the military?
(Mary laughs)
I thought she was batshit crazy.
- It's not even like that.
It's like whenever I ask
her about her home life,
she just shuts down
and I called her out on it
and we got into a huge fight
and it's why we
missed the train.
- You know, it sounds like
she's actually going
through something.
- Yeah.
- She could probably
use some support.
- I'm really trying
to be there for her.
I'm just worried that I'm
gonna say something wrong
or support her in the ways
that she doesn't need.
- I understand what you're
saying, but I don't know.
Probably the most important
thing you could do
is just listen to her
without any judgment
and then there's trust
and if you are closed
off, she'll be closed off.
You know what I mean?
- I'm really trying.
- Yeah.
(Susana snaps fingers)
- [Susana] Excuse you.
Hello?
- Yes, Ms. Santos.
How may I help you?
- A Nutri-Bar and a diet soda.
- [Denise] Will you be using
your BrainOp chip to pay today?
- Do I look like someone
that would touch cash?
- My mistake.
I will need a
verbal confirmation.
- Yes. Damn it, yes.
Get on with it.
- [Michele AI] Chip detected.
Thank you, Susana.
- Yeah.
- Have a great day.
Would you like any refreshments?
- No, that's okay.
- Okay.
May I get you anything?
- No, thank you.
I wouldn't wanna be stuck
in a zombie apocalypse
with that one.
- No. (laughs)
- I'm gonna stretch my stems.
- Okay.
(NexusTrack roaring)
(dramatic music)
- All right, everyone.
The fun is about to begin.
Let's play.
(dramatic music)
(static buzzes)
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome.
I stand before you,
just another man in
our DarkNET community.
Lumerex Corp took
credit for my AI
and the NexusTrack
that I invented.
Lumerex Corp pushed my
brilliance into the shadows.
You can steal a man's ideas,
but you cannot steal his genius.
Sometimes life works
in mysterious ways
and sometimes mysterious
ways involve revenge.
Prepare to dive boldly into
your deepest, darkest secrets,
the ones that you would
never dare reveal.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have some surprises lined up.
You gripe about other
people's behavior.
I know, constantly fantasizing
about putting them
in their place.
That prick who was rude,
that bitch who side-eyed you.
I'm giving you the opportunity
to unleash absolute
fucking chaos
no matter how perverse,
in the real world.
My goal here is $100 million,
the exact amount that
Lumerex Corp took from me.
And you people have the choice
to assist in restoring
this balance,
not only in my bank account,
but in the real world.
With our exclusive
backdoor access,
you will have the BrainOp
chip, the neural interface,
which will give you the ability
to manipulate the passengers'
thoughts, actions, emotions.
Virtual puppets.
How good does that sound?
And for you selected users,
you will have the chance
to buy in for $10 million.
With that buy-in, you
will have the opportunity
to pick any of the
selected players
from our available lineup.
Talking about a lineup,
have a look what we
have in store for you.
The creme de la creme
of the underworld.
Motley crew indeed.
(NexusTrack roaring)
- Soon as I get a chance I'm
rushing the first motherfucker
and getting the hell outta here.
- Pfft, you'll do
fucking nothing.
Either by the restraints
or with the chip,
they got us by the balls.
(NexusTrack roaring)
(NexusTrack rumbling)
- Yeah!
(laughs) Hell yeah!
It's going down, motherfuckers!
- What the fuck is going on?
Did we hit something?
(NexusTrack roaring)
- If I were you, I'd load
up your digital wallets
because with no rules
and no repercussions,
I guarantee you the
most unique experience
your money can buy.
(mysterious music)
Who will be the first
person to step up
and cause some chaos?
Show yourself.
This is your chance
to destroy things.
(suspenseful music)
Oh, come on.
You can do anything
anytime, anywhere.
Isn't that what
you always wanted?
Well, here's your
chance, my friends.
What we need here is a
financial commitment.
Talk is cheap.
So let's see who's all talk
and who's ready to make a walk?
(suspenseful music)
The rich and powerful
punch the weak
and the weak in the teeth!
(dramatic music)
Oh, what do we have here?
(chuckles) Okay, I like that.
Someone's ready
to walk the walk.
Alright.
(mysterious music)
Let's get you all dialed in.
Choose your player.
(display beeping)
Okay, there we go.
I programmed your
modules to sync up
to the nervous systems
of the selected players,
which will give you
almost immediate
mirroring capabilities.
Oh, magnificent.
My question, are you
ready to get hardcore?
- Yeah!
- Yes!
Choose your weapon.
Round one.
I'm patching you in.
(restraints click)
(prisoner grunts)
- What the fuck?
(intense music)
Yeah, where you going?
Here, let me out.
Take me with ya.
(punch thuds)
(NexusTrack roaring)
(acoustic guitar music)
(Sol singing softly)
- Bloody hell, brother.
(acoustic guitar music)
- Not bad. You've almost got it.
- Oh, thanks man.
I'm just jamming.
I'm really trying to
figure out this new tune.
But anyways, sorry if
I was bothering you.
- No, not at all.
Um, mind if I try?
- Yeah, sure thing, man.
Give it a shot.
- Alright.
Look.
(acoustic guitar music)
- Dude, that was amazing.
- It's all about finding
the right placement
and maintaining a rhythm.
- Hey, like this?
- Exactly.
- Hey, hey man, this is groovy.
Who taught you how to play?
- Uh, my wife actually.
- You guys must jam
all the time, huh?
- Uh, nah. Not in awhile.
- And why the hell not?
- That's a good question.
Yep.
(NexusTrack roaring)
(suspenseful music)
- You are still not in, Mik?
- Listen, they used to
call it supercomputer,
but this beauty right here
is a different animal.
Quantum core processors,
bio-neural circuits pulsating
with the living algorithms.
The cooling system
is so precise.
- You said you were the best.
You will do it for
your daughter's sake.
- [Mik] I'm working
as fast as I can.
(light music)
- Do you mind?
- Excuse me?
- Stop staring at me.
- Oh no, I wasn't.
I was just thinking, yeah.
- You're making
me uncomfortable.
- Oh, sorry.
- [Train Announcer] Next
up, Music City, Nashville.
- Alright.
Check please.
No chip.
Old school, pay by phone.
- Thank you. Have a nice trip.
- Thank you.
- Increase the stakes and
override the capsule speed.
Run it at max.
- If I do that,
this whole capsule
turns into an inferno.
Then what happens to me?
- If your work is
to my satisfaction,
I'll attach another capsule
and I'll extract you from
the back of the NexusTrack.
- How do I know you
will keep your word?
- Well, you don't, Mik.
But I think we both know
what your best move is here.
(keyboard clacking)
(suspenseful music)
- [Michele AI]Manual
override sequence engaged,
transitioning to a progressive
10% augmentation in velocity
scheduled at half
hour intervals.
Attention.
The provided input commands
will result in breaching
critical thresholds.
I am unable to provide
the service for critical-
System override complete.
Disengaging manual breaks.
Disengaging emergency breaks.
(train roaring)
- [Mik] Stakes are raised.
I will come back to you
once I correct public files.
- Patch me into the
monitors please.
(keyboard clacking)
- [Mik] I should
have you in soon.
(display beeping)
- Why didn't we stop?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
They didn't tell me anything.
- Ladies and gentlemen, we
apologize for the inconvenience.
We are experiencing minor
technical difficulties.
- What a circus.
- Good evening.
Welcome to the puppet show.
(suspenseful music)
- You're a cop?
- Interpol.
- The train is going
over 700 miles an hour.
No one can stop it.
You can't stop me.
You should have listened when
I said this AI was dangerous.
- Is this a fucking joke?
(dramatic music)
- This is Veronica
Chalice with World News 9
reporting live from the
NexusTrack in Oklahoma City,
bringing you all the
current and world news.
As concerns grow in Nashville,
moments ago, a capsule link blew
through the NexusTrack station
without making its
scheduled to stop.
- [Announcer]
Attention passengers.
The next NexusTrack
departure is scheduled
in 15 minutes from
platform five.
Thank you for choosing
the NexusTrack,
the safest and
fastest way to travel.
- While this unexpected
incidence raises questions,
Lumerex Corp maintains that
safety protocols are in place
and there are no issues onboard.
We will continue to
monitor this situation
and bring you updates
as they unfold.
Back to you, Chuck.
(NexusTrack roaring)
(text messages dinging)
- Who the hell was
that on the screen?
- That was Lachlan Sinquil.
He's the one who
invented BrainOp
and the AI that
runs the NexusTrack.
- I actually watched
this case on unfold,
and I think the judge
would massively disagree.
- This has to be
some kind of prank.
- Did you notice that the
train didn't stop in Nashville?
- Yeah, I did.
- I can stay here, watch them.
Lemme see if I can figure
out what's going on.
- [Scarlet] Okay.
(door rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
- It's not safe here.
You should come with me.
We'll find a safe place to hide.
(suspenseful music)
Ha ha!
- Sorry, man.
(punches thudding)
(passengers screaming)
Wow, I can really do that.
(suspenseful music)
- Try to find a weapon
to protect yourself.
- Okay, no.
What the hell is happening?
What's going on?
- Nothing you're
gonna like, honey.
- Okay, I don't
want any trouble.
- Trouble's what I paid for.
- Would sorry make a difference?
(weapon thudding)
Oh shit.
(punches thudding)
Do it!
Get him. Get him.
(weapon thudding)
- Oh! (sobbing)
- Lemme borrow this.
(passengers screaming)
(punches thudding)
(both shouting)
(weapon thudding)
(suspenseful music)
(passengers screaming)
- And you just had to
take the damn NexusTrack.
(mysterious music)
(display beeping)
- Okay. (chuckles)
Oh, I like it.
The betting boards
are out of control.
Looks like some of
you made a killing
with that gentleman
losing his tooth
in the first 10 minutes, nice,
and hey, 10 to one odds
on that lady losing
control of her bladder.
You're a sick bunch. (chuckling)
(display beeping)
You've been activated.
Have some fun.
(restraints clicking)
(suspenseful music)
- I always wanted a cock.
(prisoner laughing)
Now it's time to fuck shit up.
- Crazy son of a bitch.
(suspenseful music)
- You're boring.
Is this your bag?
Hate it.
You're hot.
You're not.
(passengers shouting)
- What the fuck?
- Hmm, where do
I sign up, coach?
Lemme show you my
spirit fingers.
- What the fuck is going on?
- My birthday is what the
fuck is going on, okay?
I just got my inheritance
and you're all
invited to the party.
It's gonna be kickass.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What was that all about?
- Oh, I hope we don't find out.
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, handsome.
You wanna dance?
(passenger screams)
- Hey, I don't want to hurt you.
- Ah!
- A little help?
- Look at you, mate.
You've got this.
- This is your
last chance, buddy.
- I just told you-
- No, not you. Him.
(energetic music)
(passengers screaming)
(kicks thudding)
(punches thudding)
- Oh, you motherfucker!
- Hey, stay back.
I'm warning you. I'm
an Interpol agent.
- Oh, what are you gonna
do, Mr. Interpol agent?
Huh? You gonna frisk me?
You gonna cuff me?
- Let's just stay back.
- Please do something.
Don't you have a
gun? Use it please!
- The capsule's pressurized.
If I miss it'll pierce the cabin
and this whole train explodes.
- Oh!
- Hey, hey, hey. It's me.
Hey man. I'm the one you
wanna dance with, huh?
Huh?
Or we can just
talk this out, huh?
(passengers scream)
I guess that's a no.
(energetic music)
(punches thudding)
Not too shabby.
I got cuffs in my bag.
Would you mind getting them?
- All right, hold him, hold him.
Oh, no, fuck!
No fucking shit!
- (laughs) Okay.
- Where am I?
- Here.
- What do you tell him?
- Told you you've got it.
- Get off me, you cunt.
- Shut the fuck up.
- What happened?
What the fuck happened? Oh geez.
It feels like I drank 20-
- Shut the fuck up.
- Oh, me head.
- Very good. Exciting, isn't it?
It's a very impressive sight,
but let's not kid ourselves.
We're nowhere near
the finish line
and the good times
are far from over.
Oh, what's this?
Okay, looks like another player
is stepping up at the plate.
I like it.
Available data indicates
significant suppressed rage.
Why don't we help
this young man out?
Anger is a very dangerous
thing to hold onto.
So let's see what he does.
Patching you in.
(NexusTrack roaring)
- Thanks.
(door rumbles)
- Ha ha!
- How long is this
going to take?
- We are almost there.
Still working on accessing
public data and chips,
but we are almost at 100.
(suspenseful music)
(NexusTrack roaring)
(door rumbles)
- I don't know who let you
freaks out of your cages,
but you are starting to
get on my last nerve.
- You know, by the
time I'm done with you,
I'm gonna show you just
how dirty I can be.
- Bring it.
(punches thudding)
(prisoner laughing)
- Baby girl, you're
turning me on.
Oh, I'm gonna enjoy this.
We're gonna have a lot of fun.
(eyeball squishing)
(body thuds)
Oh, you fucking bitch.
(head thudding)
(suspenseful music)
(Lachlan chuckles)
- I give you the
power of the gods
and you let these morons
come between your dreams?
(suspenseful music)
Seems you're scared to
spend more money, right?
Scared to hold your own
against the peasants.
That's what it looks like.
Okay, let's up the
odds a little bit.
So many fish to fry
and so little oil.
Time to go Crisco on
these motherfuckers.
(NexusTrack roaring)
- We need to find Tessa.
- I agree.
- Right.
- Guys!
Okay, I, I'm scared I can't deal
with this shit. - Hey, I know
you're scared.
I am too, but I
got you, alright?
- Listen, we need to
stay focused, alert,
and we need to stick together.
We got this, okay? Let's go.
- I have to get to my squad.
- I'm going with her.
- I'm going with you.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy.
- Calm down. It's okay.
Friendlies. Are you all right?
- It's okay.
- Some psychos are
loose on this train.
- Look out!
(passengers screaming)
(weapon thuds)
(kicks thudding)
- Goddamn, sis.
- Reflexes.
- Did you kill him?
- No, I don't think so.
He's acting completely
out of his mind.
I reckon it's that bio chip.
- I bet Lachlan Sinquil
is hacking them.
- Wait, he can do that?
- So anyone with a
chip can be hijacked?
- How many people on this train
do you reckon are chipped?
- That's a good question.
Is everybody okay in here?
- Yeah, I think so.
(cellphone ringing)
Who's that?
- Oh fuck.
- News never sleeps.
- [Roger]Susanna,
I, I hate to be the one
to tell you this, but-
- Spit it out, Roger.
- [Roger] The
Oklahoma train station
has confirmed
they've lost control
of the capsule link
that you are on.
- We blew through
the Nashville station
and suddenly there are
prisoners attacking us.
- [Roger] The newsroom
did some digging.
My sources just confirmed that
someone hijacked the train,
linked it to a capsule
transporting prisoners.
They've accessed
their BrainOp chips
and possibly tried to
take control of them all.
- Great.
- [Roger] It also looks like
they've sped up the train.
You're moving way too fast.
If you don't slow down,
you'll crash in DC.
That's if you don't overheat
first and get roasted alive.
- How much time do we have?
- I'd say about an hour.
- Right, is there anything
else we need to know?
- [Roger] They've evacuated
the DC train station.
Police and rescue
teams are standing by
at a distance of one mile
until further notice.
You're on your own in there.
- Can you tell us
anything about Lachlan?
(cellphone beeps)
Why'd you just hang up?
- This is my story.
Stop giving away the exclusive!
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
All right, fine.
If Lachlan's taken over the AI,
then we need to find out
a way to shut him down.
- Okay, if we can
find the control room,
then maybe we can
disable the mainframe
and reboot the program
and shut him out.
- Yeah, okay.
Let's take back
control of this train.
Slow it down before
it gets to DC.
(dramatic music)
- In an unfolding incident
within the NexusTrack,
initial reports indicate
a possible threat
within one of the capsule links.
Passengers have expressed
concern highlighting unsettling
and disorderly
atmosphere on board.
Official sources from Lumerex
claims that there
is no ongoing crisis
and that the NexusTrack
remains on its normal schedule.
(NexusTrack roaring)
(mysterious music)
- And I thought you were
the best of the best.
Week after week,
you were fantasizing about
causing havoc online.
Well, you spend your days
chatting about the world
that I'm providing for you.
Well, I'm providing it for you.
There it is!
Let's play.
Very good.
(restraints clicking)
(suspenseful music)
- Oh, ho, ho.
- I wanted to be Khan.
- Stop fucking whining.
I'm your big brother. I
always have the first pick.
You know that.
Besides, that's a plenty
of body for little girl.
Just make sure you
don't fucking trip, huh?
- Dick, I'm telling Mom.
- Mom?
Mom's not here to
save your fucking ass.
What you gonna do? Tell Mom?
Dumb ass.
- You're a control freak.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
- You paid 10 million to
control another person.
- So did you.
- Yes.
To kick your fucking ass and
not to get trouble for it!
That's right, that's why Dad
left me the fucking company.
Oh, come on, let's go.
- This is getting worse.
- We have to keep moving.
(passengers screaming)
Okay, I'm fed up with this shit!
If you want war,
we'll give you war.
You've got this.
- All right.
You take the one on the right.
(intense music)
(punches thudding)
- Come on!
(intense music)
- Yes!
- Hey, Interpol.
I'm gonna need you to step back.
(prisoner laughs)
- Interpol? Ooh!
- Hey guys, I said I need
you to step back and slowly-
- Fuck what you need, boy.
(prisoner laughing)
Come on. Come on.
(intense music)
Come on!
Ha ha!
(punches thudding)
(kicks thudding)
(Mary shouting)
(dramatic music)
(cellphone ringing)
- You're answering
your damn phone?
- [Roger] Can you confirm that?
Are all the prisoners chipped?
- Yeah.
From what I've seen,
they all have the
chip in their neck.
(suspenseful music)
(punch thuds)
- [Roger] You know Ivan Penn
is one of those prisoners.
- Oh shit.
He is a fucking monster.
(intense music)
(punches thudding)
(suspenseful music)
- Alright, everybody listen up.
We gotta tie those two guys up.
This one and that one.
- This one's dead.
- Listen, I have been far
down the BrainOp rabbit hole
and I found there's
a flaw with the chip,
a sound that corrupts the chips
and renders them inoperable.
They have a fail safe frequency
and I tried hacking it
and snatching the data,
but my rig didn't have the
capacity to finish the drop.
(NexusTrack roaring)
(intense music)
- Affirmative.
Initiating Operation
Clean Slate.
Ready to breach the doors,
neutralize the passengers,
and secure the capsules.
- [Boss] How long
will this take?
- Well, without guns, this
could take up to an hour,
but we'll clean up in here.
You control the media
and your reputation
will remain intact.
Are the crisis actors in place?
- [Boss] Yes.
- Good.
Convert the train to
the maintenance platform
to make the switch.
Lock that area
down, full security,
and have vehicles in
place to move the bodies.
- [Boss] Everything is in place.
You just handle your end.
- Yes, don't worry, Mr. Bennett.
By this time tomorrow,
this all will have just been
another case of fake news.
(dramatic upbeat music)
(Lachlan chuckling)
- Look who's joined the party,
a bunch of cutthroat
mercenaries, I see.
Ooh.
Looks like BloomerX is trying to
clean up their mess. Well,
that's fine with me.
Welcome.
The more the merrier.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(men grunting and groaning)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
This is an interesting twist.
That's why you never leave
before the end of the show,
ladies and gentlemen.
Question, who wants to step in
and tussle with some
trained killers?
Sounds like fun.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(upbeat music)
- Now turning our attention
to the ongoing
NexusTrack situation.
Chuck, what's the
latest on this?
- Thanks, Linda.
The situation within
the NexusTrack
has taken an unexpected turn.
Just moments ago, BloomerX
Corp issued a statement
putting to rest any
concerns about the wellbeing
and safety of the passengers.
BloomerX Corp are launching
a full investigation
into the allegations and
are threatening lawsuits
against anyone spreading
misinformation.
Linda?
- Wow, Chuck,
seems like another case of
internet gossip gone wild.
(tense upbeat music)
- We don't know how
much time we have
before another person returns.
- Well, we need to get Heather
to the control capsule.
I think we need to split up.
Those that have chips
need to stay back.
We can't let Lachlan
use them against us.
- You're not checking
me for a chip,
that's invasion of privacy.
- Oh, no, she's chipped.
We scar her skin for food.
- Bitch.
- Okay, all right, look,
I'm chipped.
(tense upbeat music continues)
I'm not gonna flip
out on everyone
like the rest of
these people, right?
- No, no, there's
levels of chip security.
Right now, I'm thinking
they're just people
under government
watch, like prisoners.
Maybe we have to tie up whoever
is chipped, just to be safe.
- That's not a bad idea.
But as you can see,
I'm not chipped myself.
- I'm not chipped
- Lachlan Saint Quill doesn't
even have that access. It would
take time to hack.
- He said he was a genius.
- And he's had plenty of time.
- No, he has not
hacked the security yet
because people who have the chip
would also be under
his command too.
- Okay, okay.
Heather, we need to get you
to that control capsule.
Let's go.
(tense upbeat music continues)
(speed train whooshes)
(dramatic upbeat music)
- To those of you
who have stayed true.
I've made a note.
I've reduced the entry fee
to the greatest game on planet
Earth for a mere $5 million.
Believe me when I
tell you things are
about to get heated up
and I don't just mean the
capsules. (speed train whooshes)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- All right, the next
carriage is the lounge,
and then after that
is the control room.
- And that's where we're going.
- Right.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(batons thudding)
(people groaning)
- [Passenger 1] Don't
kill me, don't kill me!
Please, please!
Please, please,
please, please, please!
(batons thudding)
(people groaning)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- This must be it.
- How the hell are we going
to get this door open?
- Let me try, I think I can
override the security system.
- All right, well
you guys do that.
Okay, so those freaks come back,
I reckon we need to
barricade the back door.
- Yeah, let us handle that.
You guys work on
getting this door open.
- Okay, guys, grab
tables, grab bags.
We've gotta lock the
store up, let's go.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
Are you getting close?
- I'm coding as fast as I can.
- She can do it, Coach.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- Bless monsieur.
Thank God you're here.
(knife stabbing)
(passengers screaming)
- You really need to hurry.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- Okay, they need me.
Stay here.
Watch her back.
(dramatic upbeat music fades)
(door pass keypad beeping)
(footsteps pattering)
- Come on, Heather, please.
- Told you, I'm coding
as fast as I can.
- Ah, you did it!
- Come on.
(passengers yelling)
Wait, where's the conductor?
Shouldn't someone be in here?
- That's not our problem.
We just have to find a
way into the mainframe.
You have to keep a
pretty cool distance.
(man grunting)
(hand smacking)
(woman groaning)
(monitor slamming)
(Heather groans)
(man groans)
(woman groans)
(man grunts)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- Aerial assault.
- Okay.
(man groaning and grunting)
- Okay, come on.
(dramatic upbeat music)
(men grunting)
(women screaming)
(person thuds)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(people grunting and groaning)
(bottle shatters)
(knife stabbing)
(people grunting)
(stick stabbing)
(man grunting)
- Okay, I've accessed the
control room schematics.
There is a kill switch, okay.
Theoretically we can
reboot the system
and take back control
of this thing.
- Theoretically?
- Yeah, well, I've
never done this before.
- Okay, fuck it, I trust you.
Just tell me what
you need me to do.
- Okay, you're gonna
go to the back panel.
Okay, just open it,
just open up it up.
- Good.
- Okay.
Run your fingers
along the groove
until you find a small box.
- Oh, I can't find it.
- Okay.
It's a rectangle shaped box
in the back right corner.
Just feel for it.
- Okay.
Top or bottom?
- [Heather] Top.
- Great.
(dramatic upbeat music)
- Yes, okay, I'm in.
Now we just need the data
decker to hack the code.
- Yep, okay.
- Give here.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Go.
(computer beeps)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(people grunting)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- Don't you fucking do it!
(knife stabs)
(man thuds)
(tense upbeat music)
- Oh.
- I extended an opportunity
to you all, but you failed me.
Now, let me show you how a boss
really takes care of things.
Yes!
(handcuffs clanking)
(tense upbeat music continues)
- Lets have some fun.
Fucking pussy.
(foot stomping)
(tense upbeat music continues)
(people grunting)
(shoulder snapping)
(man groaning)
(tense upbeat music continues)
(men groaning)
- Tessa!
(Tessa yelling)
(knife stabbing)
(man groaning)
(tense upbeat music continues)
(hands smacking)
(prisoner chuckling)
- Please.
(hands smacking)
(tense upbeat music continues)
(computer screen chiming)
- Okay, there's a
security protocol.
We're both gonna need to
deactivate at the same time.
I'm gonna enter the code and
you're gonna turn the gear.
Okay, search for
a circular gear.
- Yeah, I found it.
- Okay.
I got the code.
- Okay, let's stop this thing.
- Okay.
Okay, when I say, so, you're
gonna turn the cog to the left.
Pull it out, turn it 180
degrees to the right,
and then push it back in
on the count of three.
Okay?
- Okay, I'm ready.
- [Heather] Okay, ready?
One, two...
(man grunting)
(Heather screaming)
(woman grunts)
(man thuds)
(tense upbeat music continues)
(woman panting)
- It's my turn to play.
(woman screaming)
(tense upbeat music continues)
(man thuds)
Wow.
This guy is stronger than I
thought.(tense upbeat music
continues)
(hand smacking)
(woman screaming)
(tense upbeat music continues)
- Fuck me.
Bruv, I'm gonna kill this guy.
(tense upbeat music continues)
(man grunting)
Bruv!
(tense upbeat music continues)
- Fuck you.
(woman groaning)
(stick snaps)
- Shit.
(tense upbeat music continues)
- This is what you want?
(knife stabs)
(tense upbeat music fades)
- What are these
little cunts up to?
You think you can outsmart me?
Okay, let's see.
Let's see how strong your
friendship really is.
(dramatic upbeat music)
(prisoner thuds)
- What happened?
- Fuck it.
- What the fuck?
Where am I?
- Hey.
- What happened?
What the fuck is going on?
- Hey, it's okay.
(bones snapping)
(woman groans)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- Let's take this little
bitch for a test drive.
(computer screen chiming)
- Let's do this.
I'm gonna punch in the code
and then you're gonna
push the gear on three.
Ready?
One, two-
- You can't stop me.
(Heather groans)
- What the hell, Mary?
What are you doing?
- What I have to.
I put everything into this.
- Let us in!
(door banging)
Open!
- Girls, let us in, it's us!
(women grunting)
(woman groaning)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- I'm sorry.
I'll see you soon, bruv.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(man grunting)
(foot stomping)
(Heather groaning)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- I'm a fucking genius
and there is no way a little
cheerleader is gonna stop me.
(Lachlan grunting)
(Mary thuds)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(Mary grunting)
- She's got a chip.
- What the hell,
Mary, you got a chip?
(man groaning)
Mary!
- Millions of people have chips
and I'm gonna take
over their lives
as soon as I'm
done ending yours.
- Mary?
- Do I look like a
cheerleader to you?
No.
I'm the greatest inventor
of the modern age.
I'm the creator of the
tech running this train.
I am Lachlan Saint Quill.
(Lachlan laughing)
(tense upbeat music continues)
(electric signals buzzing)
(Mary thuds)
Maybe I overdid it.
- What did you do to her?
- Nothing really.
I'm just getting started.
- That is my friend that
you're fucking with!
(women grunting)
- I know that you
can fight this.
- Sorry Coach, the
chip has total control.
- Welcome to the party, Coach.
Let's dance.
- Get the hell outta my girl!
(women grunting and groaning)
(dramatic upbeat music)
(women groaning)
- This is my game.
I make the rules.
(man grunting)
Ah, you're turning on me.
I was never with you, Lachlan!
(Mary grunting)
- What are you gonna do, Coach?
- Mary, snap out of it.
I don't wanna hurt you.
- So down your chip.
It's the only way.
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
- Please help us end this.
- I don't want to do anymore.
I can't save my daughter.
It's time for me to go.
(tense upbeat music)
- Wow, wow.
You'll be lying
next to him soon.
(Mary groaning)
- You're not getting
away this time.
(man grunting)
(Mary thuds)
- Mary!
(glass shatters)
(man grunting)
(phone ringing)
- It's not the best moment.
- [Donna]Please don't tell
me you're on that NexusTrack
because-(people grunting)
- You know me, always caught
in the middle of things.
- [Donna] I'm scared.
Tell me you're gonna
make it, please?
- I can't do that,
only broken promises.
(glass shatters)
- [Donna] What was that?
- I got to go, I promise
there ain't nothing good here.
- [Donna]Please, just come home.
(dramatic upbeat music)
- Wait, hold her still.
We can test the
frequency on her.
- Fuck your frequency.
- You have the frequency?
- What do we do now?
- Just keep her
still, get her legs!
- I downloaded the file while
I was hacking the mainframe.
It's time to see if this works.
It's not gonna hurt her?
- Isn't she she
trying to hurt us?
- I'm gonna kill you!
- Do it.
- Okay.
(Mary grunting)
(frequency signal buzzing)
(Mary groaning)
- Holy shit.
Mary, Mary!
- Hey, hey...
(speed train whooshes)
(tense upbeat music)
(tense upbeat music continues)
- Time to sort this out
the old fashioned way.
(sword clinking)
(tense upbeat music continues)
- Hey, Mary,
can you hear me?
- You got this.
- Hey, Mary.
- My head.
What happened?
- Okay, yeah, I'm almost there.
Accessing audio
controls right now,
the last thing I need to do
is upload this audio file.
(frequency signal buzzing)
(people sighing and chuckling)
(sword stabbing)
(eerie instrumental music)
(Lachlan grunting)
(eerie instrumental
music continues)
- (chuckling) Wow.
Okay, so do you have any
idea of how powerful I am?
This, this was all a test.
It was an experiment to
show that I can own anyone.
I can own anything.
You don't know it,
but I already own you.
Yeah.
See, my tech is
already in the brains
of over 30 million people,
and this world,
well, it's my playground,
and you're my fucking toy.
(Lachlan grunting)
(woman groaning)
(dramatic upbeat music)
- Wait.
(man grunting)
(Lachlan thuds)
(dramatic upbeat
music continues)
(woman grunting)
- Wait!
You fell.
I know what you're thinking,
but you can't hurt me.
You have to arrest me.
I deserve a fucking trial.
(dramatic upbeat music fades)
(gentle upbeat music)
- Okay, we'll try this
again on three, all right?
- Wait, wait.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay, the brake
is on the switch.
One, two, three.
- Did it work?
(speed train screeching)
- God, yes.
- [Announcer] Initiating
emergency brake system.(speed
train screeching)
- Okay, we have to get Scarlet.
- Oh, yeah.
Okay, yeah, let's do that.
(phone ringing)
- Joey?
- Oh.
Donna.
- [Donna] Oh my
God, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Is Phyllis with you?
- [Donna] She's here.
We're so worried about you.
- Okay, tell her her dad
is gonna make it home.
(bright upbeat music)
See you.
- You guys okay?
- I don't know about
okay, but we're alive.
That's all that matters.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Lachlan fucking Saint Quill.
(tense upbeat music)
- He's fucking over.
(foot stomping)
(tense upbeat music)
- Now he's over.
- The government
has now declared
that anyone over the age
of 13 is required by law
to have the BrainOp chip
implanted by the year 2033.